{"1. What is the supreme law of the land?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "1. What is the supreme law of the land?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["the Constitution"]}, "2. What does the Constitution do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "2. What does the Constitution do?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["sets up the government", "defines the government", "protects basic rights of Americans"]}, "3. The idea of self-government is in the first three words of the Constitution. What are these words?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "3. The idea of self-government is in the first three words of the Constitution. What are these words?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["We the People"]}, "4. What is an amendment?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "4. What is an amendment?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["a change (to the Constitution)", "an addition (to the Constitution)"]}, "5. What do we call the first ten amendments to the Constitution?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "5. What do we call the first ten amendments to the Constitution?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["the Bill of Rights"]}, "6. What is one right or freedom from the First Amendment?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "6. What is one right or freedom from the First Amendment?*", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["speech", "religion", "assembly", "press", "petition the government"]}, "7. How many amendments does the Constitution have?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "7. How many amendments does the Constitution have?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["twenty-seven (27)"]}, "8. What did the Declaration of Independence do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "8. What did the Declaration of Independence do?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["announced our independence (from Great Britain)", "declared our independence (from Great Britain)", "said that the United States is free (from Great Britain)"]}, "9. What are two rights in the Declaration of Independence?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "9. What are two rights in the Declaration of Independence?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["life", "liberty", "pursuit of happiness"]}, "10. What is freedom of religion?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "10. What is freedom of religion?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["You can practice any religion, or not practice a religion."]}, "11. What is the economic system in the United States?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "11. What is the economic system in the United States?*", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["capitalist economy", "market economy"]}, "12. What is the \"rule of law\"?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "12. What is the \"rule of law\"?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " Principles of American Democracy", "answers": ["Everyone must follow the law.", "Leaders must obey the law.", "Government must obey the law.", "No one is above the law."]}, "13. Name one branch or part of the government.*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "13. Name one branch or part of the government.*", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Congress", "legislative", "President", "executive", "the courts", "judicial"]}, "14. What stops one branch of government from becoming too powerful?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "14. What stops one branch of government from becoming too powerful?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["checks and balances", "separation of powers"]}, "15. Who is in charge of the executive branch?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "15. Who is in charge of the executive branch?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the President"]}, "16. Who makes federal laws?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "16. Who makes federal laws?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Congress", "Senate and House (of Representatives)", "(U.S. or national) legislature"]}, "17. What are the two parts of the U.S. Congress?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "17. What are the two parts of the U.S. Congress?*", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the Senate and House (of Representatives)"]}, "18. How many U.S. Senators are there?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "18. How many U.S. Senators are there?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["one hundred (100)"]}, "19. We elect a U.S. Senator for how many years?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "19. We elect a U.S. Senator for how many years?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["six (6)"]}, "20. Who is one of your state's U.S. Senators now?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "20. Who is one of your state's U.S. Senators now?*", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Answers will vary. [District of Columbia residents and residents of U.S. territories should answer that D.C. (or the territory where the applicant lives) has no U.S. Senators.]"]}, "21. The House of Representatives has how many voting members?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "21. The House of Representatives has how many voting members?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["four hundred thirty-five (435)"]}, "22. We elect a U.S. Representative for how many years?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "22. We elect a U.S. Representative for how many years?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["two (2)"]}, "23. Name your U.S. Representative.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "23. Name your U.S. Representative.", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Answers will vary. [Residents of territories with nonvoting Delegates or Resident Commissioners may provide the name of that Delegate or Commissioner. Also acceptable is any statement that the territory has no (voting) Representatives in Congress.]"]}, "24. Who does a U.S. Senator represent?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "24. Who does a U.S. Senator represent?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["all people of the state"]}, "25. Why do some states have more Representatives than other states?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "25. Why do some states have more Representatives than other states?", "section": "AMERICAN GOVERNMENT", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["(because of) the state's population", "(because) they have more people", "(because) some states have more people"]}, "26. We elect a President for how many years?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "26. We elect a President for how many years?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["four (4)"]}, "27. In what month do we vote for President?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "27. In what month do we vote for President?*", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["November"]}, "28. What is the name of the President of the United States now?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "28. What is the name of the President of the United States now?*", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the name of the President of the United States."]}, "29. What is the name of the Vice President of the United States now?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "29. What is the name of the Vice President of the United States now?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the name of the Vice President of the United States."]}, "30. If the President can no longer serve, who becomes President?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "30. If the President can no longer serve, who becomes President?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the Vice President"]}, "31. If both the President and the Vice President can no longer serve, who becomes President?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "31. If both the President and the Vice President can no longer serve, who becomes President?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the Speaker of the House"]}, "32. Who is the Commander in Chief of the military?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "32. Who is the Commander in Chief of the military?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the President"]}, "33. Who signs bills to become laws?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "33. Who signs bills to become laws?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the President"]}, "34. Who vetoes bills?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "34. Who vetoes bills?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the President"]}, "35. What does the President's Cabinet do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "35. What does the President's Cabinet do?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["advises the President"]}, "36. What are two Cabinet-level positions?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "36. What are two Cabinet-level positions?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Secretary of Agriculture", "Secretary of Commerce", "Secretary of Defense", "Secretary of Education", "Secretary of Energy", "Secretary of Health and Human Services", "Secretary of Homeland Security", "Secretary of Housing and Urban Development", "Secretary of the Interior", "Secretary of Labor", "Secretary of State", "Secretary of Transportation", "Secretary of the Treasury", "Secretary of Veterans Affairs", "Attorney General", "Vice President"]}, "37. What does the judicial branch do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "37. What does the judicial branch do?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["reviews laws", "explains laws", "resolves disputes (disagreements)", "decides if a law goes against the Constitution"]}, "38. What is the highest court in the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "38. What is the highest court in the United States?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["the Supreme Court"]}, "39. How many justices are on the Supreme Court?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "39. How many justices are on the Supreme Court?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the number of justices on the Supreme Court."]}, "40. Who is the Chief Justice of the United States now?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "40. Who is the Chief Justice of the United States now?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the name of the Chief Justice of the United States."]}, "41. Under our Constitution, some powers belong to the federal government. What is one power of the federal government?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "41. Under our Constitution, some powers belong to the federal government. What is one power of the federal government?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["to print money", "to declare war", "to create an army", "to make treaties"]}, "42. Under our Constitution, some powers belong to the states. What is one power of the states?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "42. Under our Constitution, some powers belong to the states. What is one power of the states?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["provide schooling and education", "provide protection (police)", "provide safety (fire departments)", "give a driver's license", "approve zoning and land use"]}, "43. Who is the Governor of your state now?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "43. Who is the Governor of your state now?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Answers will vary. [District of Columbia residents should answer that D.C. does not have a Governor.]"]}, "44. What is the capital of your state?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "44. What is the capital of your state?*", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Answers will vary. [District of Columbia residents should answer that D.C. is not a state and does not have a capital. Residents of U.S. territories should name the capital of the territory.]"]}, "45. What are the two major political parties in the United States?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "45. What are the two major political parties in the United States?*", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Democratic and Republican"]}, "46. What is the political party of the President now?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "46. What is the political party of the President now?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the political party of the President."]}, "47. What is the name of the Speaker of the House of Representatives now?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "47. What is the name of the Speaker of the House of Representatives now?", "section": "", "subsection": " System of Government", "answers": ["Visit uscis.gov/citizenship/testupdates for the name of the Speaker of the House of Representatives."]}, "48. There are four amendments to the Constitution about who can vote. Describe one of them.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "48. There are four amendments to the Constitution about who can vote. Describe one of them.", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["Citizens eighteen (18) and older (can vote).", "You don't have to pay (a poll tax) to vote.", "Any citizen can vote. (Women and men can vote.)", "A male citizen of any race (can vote)."]}, "49. What is one responsibility that is only for United States citizens?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "49. What is one responsibility that is only for United States citizens?*", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["serve on a jury", "vote in a federal election"]}, "50. Name one right only for United States citizens.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "50. Name one right only for United States citizens.", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["vote in a federal election", "run for federal office"]}, "51. What are two rights of everyone living in the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "51. What are two rights of everyone living in the United States?", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["freedom of expression", "freedom of speech", "freedom of assembly", "freedom to petition the government", "freedom of religion", "the right to bear arms"]}, "52. What do we show loyalty to when we say the Pledge of Allegiance?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "52. What do we show loyalty to when we say the Pledge of Allegiance?", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["the United States", "the flag"]}, "53. What is one promise you make when you become a United States citizen?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "53. What is one promise you make when you become a United States citizen?", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["give up loyalty to other countries", "defend the Constitution and laws of the United States", "obey the laws of the United States", "serve in the U.S. military (if needed)", "serve (do important work for) the nation (if needed)", "be loyal to the United States"]}, "54. How old do citizens have to be to vote for President?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "54. How old do citizens have to be to vote for President?*", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["eighteen (18) and older"]}, "55. What are two ways that Americans can participate in their democracy?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "55. What are two ways that Americans can participate in their democracy?", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["vote", "join a political party", "help with a campaign", "join a civic group", "join a community group", "give an elected official your opinion on an issue", "call Senators and Representatives", "publicly support or oppose an issue or policy", "run for office", "write to a newspaper"]}, "56. When is the last day you can send in federal income tax forms?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "56. When is the last day you can send in federal income tax forms?*", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["April 15"]}, "57. When must all men register for the Selective Service?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "57. When must all men register for the Selective Service?", "section": "", "subsection": " Rights and Responsibilities", "answers": ["at age eighteen (18)", "between eighteen (18) and twenty-six (26)"]}, "58. What is one reason colonists came to America?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "58. What is one reason colonists came to America?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["freedom", "political liberty", "religious freedom", "economic opportunity", "practice their religion", "escape persecution"]}, "59. Who lived in America before the Europeans arrived?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "59. Who lived in America before the Europeans arrived?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["American Indians", "Native Americans"]}, "60. What group of people was taken to America and sold as slaves?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "60. What group of people was taken to America and sold as slaves?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["Africans", "people from Africa"]}, "61. Why did the colonists fight the British?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "61. Why did the colonists fight the British?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["because of high taxes (taxation without representation)", "because the British army stayed in their houses (boarding, quartering)", "because they didn't have self-government"]}, "62. Who wrote the Declaration of Independence?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "62. Who wrote the Declaration of Independence?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["(Thomas) Jefferson"]}, "63. When was the Declaration of Independence adopted?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "63. When was the Declaration of Independence adopted?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["July 4, 1776"]}, "64. There were 13 original states. Name three.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "64. There were 13 original states. Name three.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["New Hampshire", "Massachusetts", "Rhode Island", "Connecticut", "New York", "New Jersey", "Pennsylvania", "Delaware", "Maryland", "Virginia", "North Carolina", "South Carolina", "Georgia"]}, "65. What happened at the Constitutional Convention?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "65. What happened at the Constitutional Convention?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["The Constitution was written.", "The Founding Fathers wrote the Constitution."]}, "66. When was the Constitution written?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "66. When was the Constitution written?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["1787"]}, "67. The Federalist Papers supported the passage of the U.S. Constitution. Name one of the writers.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "67. The Federalist Papers supported the passage of the U.S. Constitution. Name one of the writers.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["(James) Madison", "(Alexander) Hamilton", "(John) Jay", "Publius"]}, "68. What is one thing Benjamin Franklin is famous for?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "68. What is one thing Benjamin Franklin is famous for?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["U.S. diplomat", "oldest member of the Constitutional Convention", "first Postmaster General of the United States", "writer of \"Poor Richard's Almanac\"", "started the first free libraries"]}, "69. Who is the \"Father of Our Country\"?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "69. Who is the \"Father of Our Country\"?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["(George) Washington"]}, "70. Who was the first President?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "70. Who was the first President?*", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Colonial Period and Independence", "answers": ["(George) Washington"]}, "71. What territory did the United States buy from France in 1803?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "71. What territory did the United States buy from France in 1803?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["the Louisiana Territory", "Louisiana"]}, "72. Name one war fought by the United States in the 1800s.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "72. Name one war fought by the United States in the 1800s.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["War of 1812", "Mexican-American War", "Civil War", "Spanish-American War"]}, "73. Name the U.S. war between the North and the South.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "73. Name the U.S. war between the North and the South.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["the Civil War", "the War between the States"]}, "74. Name one problem that led to the Civil War.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "74. Name one problem that led to the Civil War.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["slavery", "economic reasons", "states' rights"]}, "75. What was one important thing that Abraham Lincoln did?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "75. What was one important thing that Abraham Lincoln did?*", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["freed the slaves (Emancipation Proclamation)", "saved (or preserved) the Union", "led the United States during the Civil War"]}, "76. What did the Emancipation Proclamation do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "76. What did the Emancipation Proclamation do?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["freed the slaves", "freed slaves in the Confederacy", "freed slaves in the Confederate states", "freed slaves in most Southern states"]}, "77. What did Susan B. Anthony do?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "77. What did Susan B. Anthony do?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " 1800s", "answers": ["fought for women's rights", "fought for civil rights"]}, "78. Name one war fought by the United States in the 1900s.*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "78. Name one war fought by the United States in the 1900s.*", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["World War I", "World War II", "Korean War", "Vietnam War", "(Persian) Gulf War"]}, "79. Who was President during World War I?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "79. Who was President during World War I?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["(Woodrow) Wilson"]}, "80. Who was President during the Great Depression and World War II?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "80. Who was President during the Great Depression and World War II?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["(Franklin) Roosevelt"]}, "81. Who did the United States fight in World War II?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "81. Who did the United States fight in World War II?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["Japan, Germany, and Italy"]}, "82. Before he was President, Eisenhower was a general. What war was he in?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "82. Before he was President, Eisenhower was a general. What war was he in?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["World War II"]}, "83. During the Cold War, what was the main concern of the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "83. During the Cold War, what was the main concern of the United States?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["Communism"]}, "84. What movement tried to end racial discrimination?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "84. What movement tried to end racial discrimination?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["civil rights (movement)"]}, "85. What did Martin Luther King, Jr. do?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "85. What did Martin Luther King, Jr. do?*", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["fought for civil rights", "worked for equality for all Americans"]}, "86. What major event happened on September 11, 2001, in the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "86. What major event happened on September 11, 2001, in the United States?", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["Terrorists attacked the United States."]}, "87. Name one American Indian tribe in the United States.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "87. Name one American Indian tribe in the United States.", "section": "AMERICAN HISTORY", "subsection": " Recent American History and Other Important Historical Information", "answers": ["Cherokee", "Navajo", "Sioux", "Chippewa", "Choctaw", "Pueblo", "Apache", "Iroquois", "Creek", "Blackfeet", "Seminole", "Cheyenne", "Arawak", "Shawnee", "Mohegan", "Huron", "Oneida", "Lakota", "Crow", "Teton", "Hopi", "Inuit"]}, "88. Name one of the two longest rivers in the United States.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "88. Name one of the two longest rivers in the United States.", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Missouri (River)", "Mississippi (River)"]}, "89. What ocean is on the West Coast of the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "89. What ocean is on the West Coast of the United States?", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Pacific (Ocean)"]}, "90. What ocean is on the East Coast of the United States?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "90. What ocean is on the East Coast of the United States?", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Atlantic (Ocean)"]}, "91. Name one U.S. territory.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "91. Name one U.S. territory.", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Puerto Rico", "U.S. Virgin Islands", "American Samoa", "Northern Mariana Islands", "Guam"]}, "92. Name one state that borders Canada.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "92. Name one state that borders Canada.", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Maine", "New Hampshire", "Vermont", "New York", "Pennsylvania", "Ohio", "Michigan", "Minnesota", "North Dakota", "Montana", "Idaho", "Washington", "Alaska"]}, "93. Name one state that borders Mexico.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "93. Name one state that borders Mexico.", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["California", "Arizona", "New Mexico", "Texas"]}, "94. What is the capital of the United States?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "94. What is the capital of the United States?*", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["Washington, D.C."]}, "95. Where is the Statue of Liberty?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "95. Where is the Statue of Liberty?*", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Geography", "answers": ["New York (Harbor)", "Liberty Island"]}, "96. Why does the flag have 13 stripes?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "96. Why does the flag have 13 stripes?", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Symbols", "answers": ["because there were 13 original colonies", "because the stripes represent the original colonies"]}, "97. Why does the flag have 50 stars?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "97. Why does the flag have 50 stars?*", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Symbols", "answers": ["because there is one star for each state", "because each star represents a state", "because there are 50 states"]}, "98. What is the name of the national anthem?": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "98. What is the name of the national anthem?", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Symbols", "answers": ["The Star-Spangled Banner"]}, "99. When do we celebrate Independence Day?*": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "99. When do we celebrate Independence Day?*", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Holidays", "answers": ["July 4"]}, "100. Name two national U.S. holidays.": {"py/object": "__main__.question", "question": "100. Name two national U.S. holidays.", "section": "INTEGRATED CIVICS", "subsection": " Holidays", "answers": ["New Year's Day", "Martin Luther King, Jr. Day", "Presidents' Day", "Memorial Day", "Independence Day", "Labor Day", "Columbus Day", "Veterans Day", "Thanksgiving", "Christmas"]}}